{
    // Perms get: Dodo, Lemur, Bagi, Nova, Mads, Desty, Squeaks
    "Changes": [
        // Base ES
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Aideen"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Aideen loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Aideen {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{AideenFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Aideen {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Beatrice"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Beatrice loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Beatrice {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Eloise"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Eloise loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eloise {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"
                },
                // Jacob Vivienne
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Eloise loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Eloise 1 2 1, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eloise {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{EloiseFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Eloise 1 2 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eloise {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Eyvinder"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonalNegative.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Eyvinder loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Eyvinder {{MinHeartSelfSuggest}}"

                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Jacob"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jacob loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Eloise Vivienne
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Jacob loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Jacob 1 2 3 4 5, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jacob {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{JacobFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "SYNCED_CHOICE day Jacob 1 5 1 2, PLAYER_HEARTS Current Jacob {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["JosephineK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:JosephineK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Oliver
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:JosephineK loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current JosephineK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }, 
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "57873000",
                "HasSeenEvent |contains=57873005": false
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["KatarynaLK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:KatarynaLK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasFlag": "KatarynaBecomesSocial"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Leximonster"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leximonster loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:OliverK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Leximonster {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}, PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Any 57872011"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["OliverK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:OliverK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Josephine
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:OliverK loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "ANY \"SYNCED_CHOICE day OliverK 1 2 1\" \"!PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Any 57872011\", PLAYER_HEARTS Current OliverK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}, !PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Host 57873005"
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Leximonster loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "ANY \"SYNCED_CHOICE day OliverK 1 2 2\" \"PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Host 57873005\", PLAYER_HEARTS Current OliverK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}, PLAYER_HAS_SEEN_EVENT Any 57872011"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "57873000"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Rosa"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Rosa loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{RosaFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current Rosa {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["ToriLK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:ToriLK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{ToriLKFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current ToriLK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["VivienneLK"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:VivienneLK loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                "GiftTasteRelative1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteRelative1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultRelative.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:VivienneLK loved true none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true,
                    "Condition": "PLAYER_HEARTS Current VivienneLK {{MinHeartFriendSuggest}}"
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasSeenEvent": "57875000"
            }
        },
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["LumaJunimo"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:LumaJunimo loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            }
        },
        // Dodo
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["RodneyOBrien"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:RodneyOBrien loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Gus, Gunther, Leah, Elliott. When his relatives are released add a family field
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{RodneyOBrienFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "TheFrenchDodo.RodneyOBrien"
            }
        },
        // Nora
        {
            "Action": "EditData",
            "Target": "spacechase0.SpaceCore/Questions",
            "TargetField": ["Nora"],
            "Entries": {
                "GiftTastePersonal1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTastePersonal1",
                    "Weight": 15,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftTaste}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultPersonal.{{Random:{{Range:1,12}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:Nora loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                },
                // Friends Tori Eli Dylan
                "GiftTasteFriend1": {
                    "ID": "GiftTasteFriend1",
                    "Weight": 10,
                    "QuestionText": "{{i18n:AskForGiftSuggestion}}",
                    "AnswerText": "{{i18n:DefaultFriend.{{Random:{{Range:1,11}}}}{{poohnhi.PoohCore/GetGiftTasteCPTokenFromSomeOne:{{Random:{{NoraFriends}}}} loved false none}}}}",
                    "CanRepeatQuestion": true
                }
            },
            "When": {
                "HasMod": "Bagi.Nora.CP"
            }
        },
    ]
}